# SON CAO

SYSTEM ENGINEER, DEVOPS ENGINEER, AUTOMATION ENGINEER 

● HA NOI, VIET NAM 

● 0855188833

# • DETAILS •

124/73/7 Au Co Street Ha Noi Viet Nam 0855188833 caothanhson48@gmail.com

Date of birth 04/08/1991

# SKILLS

Cloud, Azure, AWS, GCP

Docker, Nomad, Kubernetes

Terraform, Ansible

Python, Linux

# PROFILE

I have more than 6 years of general experience in the IT world. performed several roles such as Automation Engineer, System Engineer, DevOps Engineer, Quality Assurance Engineer, Technical Support

I like to make everything work smoothly, balance between manual and automated, I'm confident working independently or as part of a team. I can learn new thing quite quick and willing to take challenge tasks.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

## DevOps Engineer / Site Reliability Engineer at One Mount Group, Ha Noi

December 2019 — Present

- Design and setup infrastructure CI/CD pipeline for new development project.
- Making improvement about workflow, pipeline, build speed, architecture, system reliability, monitoring.
- Support and troubleshooting infrastructure, environment, network, deployment and runtime issue
- Migrate services from DC to Google Cloud.
- Build and maintain centralized DevOps tools

# DevOps Engineer at Niteco, Ha Noi

March 2019 — December 2019

- Setup DevOps life cycle and Managed Services process
- Proactive handle and support client via the ticket system and on-call
- · Design and build up system architecture on Cloud

#### Automation Engineer for Telstra at FPT Software, Ha Noi

March 2018 — March 2019

- Manage and optimize infrastructure and enterprise applications, satisfy all stakeholders.
- Respond to high severity production issues escalated by operations teams
- · Contribute to the migration strategy of Atlassian applications to AWS
- Work closely with the development team to ensure the successful deployment and operation of their application.
- Support thousands of users in the Atlassian ecosystem: Tools configuration, problem investigating, suggest best practice.

#### AWS Cloud Engineer for Essent at FPT Software, Ha Noi

June 2017 — March 2019

- Manage and operate a large scale system on AWS
- Monitoring Infrastructure, Application 24/7
- Contribute to system architecture design.
- Technical support for client
- · Proactively monitoring customer system and application

#### Quality Assurance Engineer, Ha Noi

2015 - 2017

- Working on Product Kofax Total Agility and Kofax Front Office Server
- Study requirement and design test case, test charter, test script. Run daily Automation test and manual test.
- Maintain Test Environment in the Azure cloud.

- Support developer in fixing bug and troubleshoot problem,
- Daily Report and communicate with team in USA.

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor, Genetic Bach Khoa, Ha Noi

2009 - 2014

# **★** CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Certified Azure DevOps Engineer Expert

August 2019 — August 2021

Microsoft Certified Azure Solution Architect Expert

May 2019 — May 2021

**Microsoft Certified Azure Administrator Associate** 

July 2019 — July 2021

# **AWS Certified Solution Architect Associate**

December 2017 — December 2020

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/b2470cfb-b672-439d-a7b1-41b9b9133c8b/public\_url